A Guide to the Special Collections Donor Correspondence Files, 1990-2007
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections Donor Correspondence Files 1990-2007
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-12/11/4.051
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student and employee records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.) and the Freedom of Information Act (F.O.I.A.). In addition, the collection may contain confidential donor information.
Acquisition Information
These papers were transferred internally from the Special Collections working departmental files on February 10, 2005 and May 4, 2007.
Scope and Content
The papers consist chiefly of correspondence of Special Collections with donors, particularly letters of acknowledgment for gifts received, 1990-2007. The files contain ca. 2,000 items (7 Hollinger boxes, ca. 3 linear feet).
Arrangement
This collection is arranged alphabetically by the name of the donor in either folders for individuals or a general alphabetical file. The general alphabetical files are arranged chronologically within each folder.
Contents List
- A- General, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 1:1)
- Agelasto, Peter A. III, 1995 (Box-folder 1:2)
  Includes an article Two on Pegasus: Robert Frost and J.J. Lankes by Welford Dunaway Taylor.
- American Rhododendron Society, 2002 (Box-folder 1:3)
- Arnold, Matthew, 1992 (Box-folder 1:4)
- Auchincloss, Louis S., 1990-1996 (Box-folder 1:5)
- B- General, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 1:6)
- B- General, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 1:7)
- Bart Memorial, 1995 (Box-folder 1:8)
- Book Arts Press, 1992 (Box-folder 1:9)
- Bolton, Aurelia, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 1:10)
- Brucolli, Matthew, 1996-2007 (Box-folder 1:11)
- C- General, 1990-1999 (Box-folder 1:12)
- Caldwell, Erskine, 1990-1998 (Box-folder 1:13)
- Carpenter, Nan Cooke, 1993 (Box-folder 2:1)
- Chappell, Warren, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 2:2)
- Cheuse, Alan, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 2:3)
- Craddock, Charles, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 2:4)
- D- General, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 2:5)
- Danowski, Raymond, 1994-2002 (Box-folder 2:6)
- Davenport, Braxton, including a 1931 index of H.B. Davenport's Library, 1931, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 2:7)
- Dawson, S. Cooper, Jr., 1992-1994 (Box-folder 2:8)
- E- General, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 2:9)
- Evans, Mrs. Daniel Webster, 1977-1993 (Box-folder 2:10)
- F- General, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 2:11)
- Flowers, Maury, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 2:12)
- Frost, Robert, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 2:13)
- Fuller, Benjamin, 1932, 1975-1995 (Box-folder 2:14)
  Includes original correspondence with President John Lloyd Newcomb with Bladen T. Tayloe.
- G- General, 1993-2002 (Box-folder 3:1)
- Gordon, Henry S., 1977-1989 (Box-folder 3:2)
- Gordon, Henry S., 1990-2001 (Box-folder 3:3)
- Gordon, Mrs. Douglas, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 3:4)
- Gordon, Mrs. Douglas, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 3:5)
- Graham Collection, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 3:6)
- Gwathmey Proposal, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 3:7)
- H- General, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 3:8)
- H- General, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 3:9)
- Harrison, Thomas, 2002 (Box-folder 3:10)
- Holsinger Proposal, 1996 (Box-folder 4:1)
- Holsinger Studio, 1992 (Box-folder 4:2)
- I- General, 1998 (Box-folder 4:3)
- Irving, Washington, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 4:4)
- J- General, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 4:5)
- K- General, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 4:6)
- Kenwood Estate, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 4:7)
- Kullikowski, Mrs. Leon T., 1998-1999 (Box-folder 4:8)
- L- General, 1993-2002 (Box-folder 4:9)
- Lang, Cecil, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 4:10)
- Levine, Leonard, 1993-2000 (Box-folder 4:11)
- Lorentz, Henrik A., 1982-1997 (Box-folder 4:12)
- Mc- General, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 4:13)
- McCray, Benjamin, 1996 (Box-folder 4:14)
- McGregor Foundation, 1988-1994 (Box-folder 4:15)
- McIlhenny, John S., 1991-1994 (Box-folder 4:16)
- M- General, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 4:17)
- M- General, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 5:1)
- Maass, Richard, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 5:2)
- Maclean, Sir Fitzroy, 1998-1999, 2003 (Box-folder 5:3)
- Manuscripts- General, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 5:4)
- Moore, John Travers, 1992-1998 (Box-folder 5:5)
- Moore, John Travers- Estate, 1995 (Box-folder 5:6)
- Morris, William, 1969-1993 (Box-folder 5:7)
- N- General 1993-1998 (Box-folder 5:8)
- Nau, John, 1999 (Box-folder 5:9)
- Nelson, W. R., 1998 (Box-folder 5:10)
- O- General, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 5:11)
- P- General, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 5:12)
- Payne, Clara Ellis, 1993 (Box-folder 5:13)
- Peale, Robert, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 6:1)
- Presler, Mr. and Mrs. Henry H., 1993 (Box-folder 6:2)
- Q- General, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 6:3)
- R- General, 1993-2000 (Box-folder 6:4)
- Ribble, Fred, 1984-1996 (Box-folder 6:5)
- Riggs Stamp Collection, 1994 (Box-folder 6:6)
- Riley, Herbert Parks, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 6:7)
- S- General, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 6:8)
- S- General, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 6:9)
- Scott, Mrs. M. Dupont, 1983-2000 (Box-folder 6:10)
- Shackelford, George G., 1990-1992 (Box-folder 6:11)
- Shaffett, Maupin, 1996 (Box-folder 6:12)
- Sieg, J. Wallace, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 6:13)
- Stubbs, Kendon L., 2001 (Box-folder 6:14)
- T- General, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 7:1)
- Taylor, Helen Marie, 1989-1994 (Box-folder 7:2)
- Taylor, Peter, 1995 (Box-folder 7:3)
- Thomas Jefferson Foundation, 2002 (Box-folder 7:4)
- Tunstall, Mrs. Robert B., 1967-1973 (Box-folder 7:5)
- Tunstall, Mrs. Robert B., 1974-1977 (Box-folder 7:6)
- Tunstall, Mrs. Robert B., 1978-1990 (Box-folder 7:7)
- U- General, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 7:8)
- V- General, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 7:9)
- W- General, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 7:10)
- W- General, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 7:11)
- Y- General, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 7:12)
- Z- General, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 7:13)